<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

    <string id="ammo-6.8x43_fmj">
        <text>6.8x43 FMJ</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ammo-6.8x43_fmj_descr">
        <text>The 6.8 Remington Special Purpose round is a rifle round that was developed by Remington Arms in collaboration with members of the U.S. Army to possibly replace the 5.56 NATO round. It is midway between the 5.56x45mm NATO and 7.62x51mm NATO in diameter and muzzle energy, slightly more powerful than the 7.62x39 round. </text>
    </string>

    <string id="ammo-6.8x43_sst">
        <text>6.8x43 SST</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ammo-6.8x43_sst_descr">
        <text>Short for "Super Shock Tip" the SST round is designed to deliver tremendous shock on impact while expanding quickly and reliably.</text>
    </string>

	<string id="ammo-50_beowulf_jfp">
		<text>.50 Beowulf JFP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-50_beowulf_jfp_descr">
		<text>Jacketed flat point  .50 Beowulf (12.7x42) rounds. The bullet expands on impact, crushing through body armor and causing tremendous tissue damage.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ammo-50_beowulf_hp">
		<text>.50 Beowulf HP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ammo-50_beowulf_hp_descr">
		<text>Hollow point .50 Beowulf (12.7x42) rounds. The bullet framents on impact causing tremendous damage to soft tissue.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_wpn_ak15">
		<text>AK-15</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak15_descr">
		<text>The AK-15 is a variant of the AK-12 chambered in 7.62x39, allowing for the use of standard AK-47 and AKM magazines. Like the base AK-12, the rifle comes standard with Picatinny rails, an adjustable telescoping stock and the rear sight has been moved to the back of the receiver. The rifle has a new muzzle brake and improved rifling, making it more accurate than other AK-47 variants. Its main drawbacks are the higher recoil and heavier weight compared to its 5.45x39 cousin.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_lr680">
        <text>LR-680</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_lr680_descr">
        <text>A variant of the 5.56x45mm LR-300 assault rifle chambered for the larger 6.8mm SPC round. Due to its larger round, its fire rate is noticeably lower compared to the standard LR-300, but features a higher damage output.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] NATO silencer\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m4bm">
        <text>Bushmaster M4</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_m4bm_descr">
        <text>The Bushmaster M4 is a copy of the popular M4 carbine manufactured by Bushmaster Firearms International, modeled on the AR-15 platform and chambered in 6.8 SPC.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] NATO silencer\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m4_brec7">
        <text>Barrett REC7</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_m4_brec7_descr">
        <text>An M16 rifle rechambered for the more powerful 6.8x43 SPC round and fires in semi-automatic and full automatic firemodes, boosting higher firepower then its 5.56x45mm variant but higher recoil due to its larger round.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] NATO silencer\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher (after modification)</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_50">
		<text>Beowulf M4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_50_descr">
		<text>The Beowulf M4 is a fully automatic variant of the M4 carbine chambered in .50 Beowulf. The round is intended to improve stopping power greatly at short- to medium-range as compared to the standard 5.56x45mm NATO round. One of its advertised uses is at vehicle checkpoints, since the heavy bullet's flight path is not easily deflected by auto glass or standard vehicle body panels. Although much has been written about its tactical uses, the .50 Beowulf is gaining recognition as a sporting cartridge. It is becoming more widely recognized as being usable by stalkers for hunting against the Zone's creatures. \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] NATO silencer\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher (after modification)</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m249_nimble">
        <text>M68</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_m249_nimble_descr">
        <text>The M68 is a customized M249 machine gun rechambered in 6.8 SPC.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] NATO silencer\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes</text>
    </string>

</string_table>