<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

    <string id="st_wpn_vepr_ar">
		<text>Vepr 7.62</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr_ar_descr">
		<text> The Vepr was the first indigenous Ukranian assult rifle, it was announced in 2003 and designed by the State Space Agency of Ukraine. It was made to replace the AKM and AK-74 in Ukranian service and was proclaimed to possess revolutionary upgrades over the AK-74. Practically, the rifle is a bullpup conversion of the AKM and boasts similar performance to the AK-74M. The bullpup configuration results in a more compact rifle, however this comes with ergonomical drawbacks and a heavy trigger pull. The rifle never saw widespread use, limited numbers found their way into the hands of servicemen and are a rare sight in the zone. A few of these rifles were also converted to the 7.62x39mm cartridge, accepting standard AKM magazines.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 scope \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vepr_ar_custom">
		<text>Vepr</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr_ar_custom_descr">
		<text> The Vepr was the first indigenous Ukranian assult rifle, it was announced in 2003 and designed by the State Space Agency of Ukraine. It was made to replace the AKM and AK-74 in Ukranian service and was proclaimed to possess revolutionary upgrades over the AK-74. Practically, the rifle is a bullpup conversion of the AKM and boasts similar performance to the AK-74M. The bullpup configuration results in a more compact rifle, however this comes with ergonomical drawbacks and a heavy trigger pull. The rifle never saw widespread use, limited numbers found their way into the hands of servicemen and are a rare sight in the zone. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 scope \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 suppressor \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpk_drum">
		<text>RPK (drum)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk_drum_descr">
		<text>The RPK is a Soviet light machine gun, developed by Mikhail Kalashnikov in 1961 based on the Kalashnikov assault rifle. Created as part of Soviet efforts to standardise the armoury of the Red Army, the RPK replaced the RPD and is still in use to present day. The 75 round drum augments its firepower, but increases weight and makes the weapon more unwieldy. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-8-02 Kobra, ACOG, PSO-1 scopes \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12_drum">
		<text>Vepr-12 (drum)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12_drum_descr">
		<text>The Vepr-12 is a multi-purpose semi-automatic shotgun, created by Molot-Oruzhie Ltd. It is patterned after Kalashnikov rifles, and built on the heavy RPK light machine gun receiver. Like the Kalashnikov rifle, it is a rotating bolt, gas operated gun that feeds from a 20 round drum magazine.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-8-02 Kobra, 1P29, PSO-1 scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_cbj">
		<text>Saab-Bofors CBJ PDW</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cbj_descr">
		<text>Saab CBJ-MS PDW is a Swedish submachine gun designed for personal defence weapon (PDW) role. It is a small and compact submachine gun of modular construction that can be chambered in 9x19mm and 6.5x25mm CBJ ammunition, but ambitious zone technicians have rechambered this particular weapon to 5.7x28mm FN. It is a blowback-operated, selective fire submachine gun which is based on the Israeli Uzi submachine gun. Among it's features is unusual equipment for an SMG such as a bipod, 100-round magazine, frontal grip which can also act like spare magazine housing and an optics rail. The CBJ is relatively lightweight at 2.8kg, but compared to modern PDWs with polymer parts it is heaviest of them all. In The Zone the CBJ is very rare, only a few came with Mercenary squads who use these weapons to improve their firepower. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_spectre">
		<text>SITES Spectre M4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spectre_descr">
		<text>The Spectre M4 is a 9x19mm submachine gun developed in 1980s by Italian manufacturer SITES for use by counter-terrorist and police units. It has a compact design and high rate of fire. Very short barrel and compact size place it close to weapons such as MP5K or Kiparis. High-capacity magazines hold 50 rounds of 9x19mm rounds, which allows for prolonged shooting, even though the weapon shoots very rapidly at 850 rounds per minute. Overally, the Spectre is a very compact submachine gun/machine pistol hybrid, but it's capacity and firepower is pretty high. In The Zone, Spectre submachine guns are sometimes available on black market and are well liked for their great handling, low weight and compact size, making it very good weapon for scavengers and artifact hunters who don't need a fighting weapon and just want something light to carry on them for personal defense from mutants and bandits at close range. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mg36">
        <text>MG36</text>
    </string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mg36_descr">
        <text>The MG36 is the Light Machine Gun variant of the H&amp;K G36 Assault Rifle. It is fitted with a 100 round Beta C-Mag magazine, a heavy barrel and a bipod, it fires the standard 5.56mm NATO cartridge like the other variants of the G36 family. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n \n</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_gl">
		<text>FN F2000 GL</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_gl_descr">
		<text>From the late 1980s to early 1990s, FN Herstal began to develop a new rifle. The aim was to produce a modern and modular weapon resulting in the FN F2000 rifle, first displayed to the public in 2001. The F2000 offers all of the popular features of the modern assault rifle such as a compact bullpup layout, ambidextrous handling and a modular design with plenty of options and addons available. So far, the FN F2000 rifle has found only a few buyers, including the Armed Forces of Slovenia and Belgian Special Operations Forces.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] FN2000 scope (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GL1 grenade launcher (integrated) \n \n</text> 
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fnfalo">
		<text>FN FALO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnfalo_descr">
		<text>The FN FALO (French, Fusil Automatique Lourd) is a Squad Automatic Weapon variant of the iconic FN FAL. Compared to the standard FAL, the FALO features a heavier barrel, bipod, and 30 round magazine. Unlike the FAL, the FALO only saw limited adoption, most notably by the Canadian military as the C2A1 and Australia as the L2A1. In its role the FALO was not very well liked, with both its comparatively light weight and 30 round capacity limiting its ability to provide accurate, sustained automatic fire. The FALO was eventually replaced in service by variants of the FN Minimi. This particular gun has been modified to a pseudo DMR configuration, repositioning its bipod and mounting a variable power optic, however, its accuracy is lower than a purpose built DMR. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x40 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mac">
		<text>MAC Model 10</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mac_45_descr">
		<text>The Military Armament Corporation Model 10, officially abbreviated as "M10" or "M-10", and more commonly known as the MAC-10, is a compact, blowback operated machine pistol/submachine gun that was developed by Gordon B. Ingram in 1964. It is chambered in either .45 ACP or 9mm. A two-stage suppressor by Sionics was designed for the MAC-10, which not only abates the noise created, but makes it easier to control on full automatic (although it also makes the gun far less compact and concealable). \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP suppressor </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mac11">
		<text>MAC Model 11</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mac11_descr">
		<text>The Ingram MAC-11 (Military Armament Corporation Model 11) is a subcompact machine pistol/submachine gun developed by American gun designer Gordon Ingram at the Military Armament Corporation (MAC) during the 1970s in Powder Springs, Georgia. The weapon is a sub-compact version of the Model 10 (MAC-10), and is chambered to fire the smaller .380 ACP round or 9mm. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m16a4_sniper">
		<text>M16A4 SAM-R</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a4_sniper_descr">
		<text>The US Squad Advanced Marksman Rifle (SAM-R) is a heavily modified M16-series rifle intended to provide increased accuracy at longer ranges, giving infantry squads greater firepower. It is basically an M16A4 outfitted with heavier, accurized, stainless-steel barrel, two-stage match trigger and a high-power Leupold scope. The barrel is free-floating with special type of handguard which doesn't come into contact with barrel. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold 3-9x36 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp9">
		<text>Brugger-Thomet MP9-N</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp9_descr">
		<text>MP9 is a compact machine pistol designed and manufactured by Brugger and Thomet Co. of Switzerland. In itself it is a further development of Steyr TMP project, which was sold by Steyr in 2001. The MP9 shoots with high rate of fire of 900 rounds per minute, but is relatively easy to control and comfortable to shoot. The MP9-N is a further refined variant, firing at an increased 1100 rpm. It is effective as PDW or for concealed carry for security and bodyguards. It is currently used by multiple police and security forces, among them ones from France, Switzerland and Thailand. To augment its role as a PDW, certain technicians with more skill than reason have converted some of these guns to 5.7x28. The result is a surprisingly effective, low cost alternative to the P90. \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rspartan">
		<text>SPR 453 (auto)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rspartan_descr">
		<text>The Remington Spartan 453, also known as the SPR 453, is a gas operated semi-automatic shotgun. It is an American import of the Russian-made Baikal MP-153, manufactured by Izhevsk Mechanical Plant in Izhevsk, Russia, marketed and distributed by Remington Arms. Aftermarket modifications have enabled this gun to achieve fully automatic fire. While the substantial recoil, high cyclic rate and low capacity of this gun limits its practicality, it still remains devastating in close quarters. \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aek919k">
		<text>AEK-919K Kashtan</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek919k_descr">
		<text>The AEK-919K Kashtan is a Russian select-fire submachine gun, chambered for the 9x19mm Parabellum and 9x18mm Makarov rounds, developed by the Kovrov Mechanical Plant. The AEK-919 is offered as a weapon for certain categories of personnel (crews of aircraft and combat vehicles), as well as special forces of law enforcement agencies. Its compact size has led some to utilize it as a sidearm, where its increased controllability comes at the cost of handling and weight. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_desert">
		<text>MK18 CQBR (camouflaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_desert_descr">
		<text>The Mk18 is a special shortened carbine with commando-length barrel for improved handling and lower weight. The Mk18 is in essence an M4A1 carbine outfitted with Close Quarter Battle Receiver (CQBR) - a replacement upper receiver featuring a 10.3" (262mm) barrel. The shorter barrel makes the weapon significantly more compact and easier to use in and around vehicles and tight confined spaces. The Mk18 is praised for its light weight and short dimensions, making it very easy to handle. It has its drawbacks, however. The short barrel provides insufficient velocity for the bullet to display ideal wounding characteristics. Nonetheless, the Mk18 is a very good weapon in its niche and while it lacks universality of 14"-20"-barreled rifles it remains highly effective when used in suitable situations. This specific gun has been further specialized for CQC operations, featuring a 60 round quad stack magazine, increased rate of fire, and holographic sight. These features have increased its weight and decreased handling, though the increased firepower more than makes up for the cost. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EOTech sight (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pm_drum">
		<text>Makarov PM (drum magazine)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_drum_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is the most common pistol in the Zone and is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. It is small, highly reliable, easy to use and maintain in working order. It also suffers from several drawbacks, including short range, low firing accuracy and poor stopping power, while also losing out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight and magazine size. In 1951, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy, and reasonable stopping power. This gun features an 80 round drum, which was made to allow for sustained firepower with a single hand, typically in a police role alongside a shield. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_raffica">
		<text>Beretta 93R</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_raffica_descr">
		<text>The Beretta 93R, also known as Raffica (Italian: "Burst") is a selective-fire machine pistol chambered in 9x19mm and developed in the late 1970s. It is a heavily redesigned Beretta 92, it uses the same base and system, but has differences such as a fire selector with semi and burst mode, in which it fires three rounds with cyclic rate of 1100RPM. It has a crude vertical grip and a ported barrel to reduce muzzle climb, however it is still considered to be hard to control in burst fire mode. It was used in limited numbers of Italian counter-terrorists, Carabinieri, police and paramilitary forces as a PDW. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vbr">
		<text>VBR PDW</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vbr_descr">
		<text>The VBR-PDW is a double-action personal defense weapon chambered for 7.92?24mm rounds, designed and manufactured by VBR-Belgium. It is a select-fire weapon with a retractable buttstock and integrated foregrip. It also has three in-built sights; iron sights, as well as two flip-up aperture sights. It can also be chambered in 9x19mm Parabellum. The weapon takes standard double-stacked Glock magazines. This gun has been rechambered to 5.7x28mm, providing an alternative to the FN Five-seveN. \n \n 
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.7x28 compatible suppressor </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_g18c">
		<text>Glock 18C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g18c_descr">
		<text>The Glock 18C is a 9x19mm machine pistol based on the Glock 17, a modern polymer-framed, striker-fired pistol developed in the late 1970s in Austria. It has a fire selector mounted by default which has two positions, semi and full-auto, which, due to non-modified action, fires with extremely high cyclic rate of 1200RPM. The G18C additionally has a ported barrel to act as compensator to reduce muzzle rise in fully-automatic mode. The Glock 18 was adopted by multiple countries' militaries, special forces units and police departments. Glock 18 machine pistols are not available to civilians and are usually much more expensive than standard Glock pistols. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GemTech suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_psg1">
		<text>HK SR9 TC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_psg1_descr">
		<text>The Heckler and Koch SR9 is a series of hunting and target rifles derived from the Heckler &amp; Koch HK91 incorporating parts from the PSG-1 and MSG-90 marksman rifles. In its original configuration it had a thumbhole buttstock, but the SR9 TC (Target Competition) variant replaces this with a PSG-1 adjustable butstock, also including the PSG-1 sniper trigger group and handgrip. As only limited numbers of SR9 TC rifles were produced, it is likely this is a reproduction, created with aftermarket parts and made to better mimic the appearance of the original PSG-1. This rifle's accuracy is not to the level of a true PSG-1, however it is significantly lighter and more durable, allowing it to better function as a DMR.  \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Hensoldt ZF PSG-1 6x42 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_remington870_slug">
		<text>Remington 870 (rifled)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington870_slug_descr">
		<text>Remington 870 is an American gun, first introduced in 1950 by Remington Arms. Due to its characteristic recharge is one of the most famous pump-action rifles in the world. Produced in various versions, it is suitable for both the military and the police, for hunters and athletes, as well as for self-defense. This 870 has been customized for hunting with slugs, featuring a magnified optic and rifled barrel, allowing for better stabilization and accuracy but precluding the ability to shoot buckshot. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold FX-I Rimfire 4x28 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_saiga_bp">
		<text>Saiga-12S Bullpup</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga_bp_descr">
		<text>This is a custon bullpup configuration shotgun, derived from a Saiga-12S. This gun originated as some gunsmith's personal project, how it got into the Zone is anyone's guess. Several modifications were made, including the relocation of the charging handle to the left side of the receiver. As a result of these modifications, this gun features slightly improved accuracy and less felt recoil than a conventional Saiga, though its cyclic rate has beeen reduced as a result. Its small size also improves its suitability to close quarters operations, though the bullpup configuration may feel awkward to some. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_cool">
		<text>AKS-74UN OKP-7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_cool_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range. This is a rare variant, preferred by some of the elites within the zone and found only in their hands. The only way to obtain one of these rifles is to take it from the hands of its previous owner, a status symbol within the Zone. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] OKP-7 scope (integrated) \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 suppressor \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hk51">
		<text>HK51</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_wpn_hk51_descr">
		<text>The HK51 is a shortened variant of G3 battle rifle. Contrary to popular belief, it was not developed by Heckler and Koch, but Fleming Arms for British Special Forces. The HK51's short size improves handling but reduces reliability and makes the rifle more prone to overheating. The short barrel also results in a brighter muzzle flash and louder sound signature, together with increased recoil, which is already pretty high due to powerful 7.62x51mm round. The round also loses some muzzle velocity, lowering its power. The HK51 got adopted by SAS and SBS, but because of its faults it was withdrawn following the introduction of HK53 carbines using 5.56x45mm rounds that were more suitable for commando-length (~9-12.5" barrel) carbines. HK51 was later introduced into free market in semi-automatic variant, made from HK91 rifles (a civilian semi-auto variant of G3) and adapted to use MP5 furniture. The HAMR scope mounted to this example allows for rapid acquisition of both close and mid-range targets. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] HAMR scope (integrated) </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_psg1a1">
		<text>HK PSG-1A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_psg1a1_descr">
		<text>The PSG-1 is a precision rifle based on the G3 battle rifle. It was designed from the beginning as a police sniper rifle for maximum precision. It boasts very high accuracy, but is also extremely expensive, leading to limited sales and a cessation of production in 2010. After the 1972 Munich massacre, Germany needed a semi-automatic rifle that would provide highest precision possible, eventually resulting in this gun and the WA2000. Mechanically it is just like the G3, though with features lending to higher precision. The PSG-1's accuracy is close to that of bolt-action sniper rifles, which is exceptional for a semi-automatic weapon. The rifle's weight, price and rather delicate construction makes it unsuitable for military use, leading to the development of the MSG90, with improvements aimed towards military conditions. The PSG-1A1 variant features 2 main improvements, an adjustment to the charging handle's position to prevent interference with optics, and an update to a Schmidt &amp; Bender 3–12?50 Police Marksman II scope.  \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Schmidt &amp; Bender 3-12x50 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_groza_545">
		<text>OTs-14-2A Groza</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_545_descr">
		<text>The OTs-14-2A is an experimental model of the "Groza" bullpup assault rifle, chambered in 5.45x39mm. It was never fully developed due to a preference for the superior performance of 7.62x39mm through the given barrel length. This is a custom zone creation, emulating the experimental variant by meticulously replacing the barrel and allowing the gun to fire the more common 5.45x39mm cartridge. It has also been modified to use the more widely available PSO-1 scope. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 scope \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_groza_tactical">
		<text>Groza Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_tactical_descr">
		<text>A rare variant of the OTs-14 Groza bullpup rifle, tailored for covert operations within the zone. This weapon features an integrated suppressor and Picatinny rails that facilitate the mounting of a variety of optics, but no longer possesses an integrated grenade launcher. The gun has also been chambered in the common 5.45x39mm cartridge to allow for simpler resupplying over potentially long expeditions. It is the preferred weapon of some military stalkers. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45 integrated suppressor \n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PO4x34, ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, C-more Railway Tactical, EOTech scopes \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_big_ben">
		<text>"Big Ben"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_big_ben_descr">
		<text>A custom form of Desert Eagle, taking a gun that is already powerful and reworking it to fire rifle bullets. How this is accomplished is not known, but these guns are a favorite of certain type of Scientist. \n \n 
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DeltaPoint Sight (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aa12">
		<text>AA-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_descr">
		<text>The AA-12 (Auto Assault-12), originally designed and known as the Atchisson Assault Shotgun, is an automatic combat shotgun developed in 1972 by Maxwell Atchisson. The most prominent feature is its constant recoil system, reducing felt recoil. The current 2005 version has been developed over 18 years since the patent was sold to Military Police Systems, Inc. The original design was the basis of several later weapons, including the USAS-12 combat shotgun. The shotgun fires in fully automatic mode only. However, the relatively low cyclic rate of fire of around 300 rounds per minute enables the shooter to fire semi-automatically de facto with brief trigger pulls. It is fed from either an 8-shell box magazine, or a 20- or 32-shell drum magazine. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ATG suppressor \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_cust">
		<text>AA-12 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_cust_descr">
		<text>The AA-12 (Auto Assault-12), originally designed and known as the Atchisson Assault Shotgun, is an automatic combat shotgun developed in 1972 by Maxwell Atchisson. The most prominent feature is its constant recoil system, reducing felt recoil. The current 2005 version has been developed over 18 years since the patent was sold to Military Police Systems, Inc. The original design was the basis of several later weapons, including the USAS-12 combat shotgun. The shotgun fires in fully automatic mode only. However, the relatively low cyclic rate of fire of around 300 rounds per minute enables the shooter to fire semi-automatically de facto with brief trigger pulls. It is fed from either an 8-shell box magazine, or a 20- or 32-shell drum magazine. This example includes a low magnification optic, as well as a couple other additional accessories. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] AC11090 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_g36_heavy">
        <text>MG36E</text>
    </string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36_heavy_descr">
        <text>The MG36 is the Light Machine Gun variant of the H&amp;K G36 Assault Rifle. It is fitted with a 100 round Beta C-Mag magazine, a heavy barrel and a bipod, it fires the standard 5.56mm NATO cartridge like the other variants of the G36 family. The MG36E is the export version of the MG36, it lacks the distinctive dual sight, but allows the mounting of alternate optics. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG sight \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n \n</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svd_ghillie">
		<text>SVD Ghillie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_ghillie_descr">
		<text>Originally intended for designated marksmen in every basic Soviet infantry unit, the Dragunov SVD was not designed for specialised sniper teams. Relatively light for a sniper rifle but well-balanced and having semiautomatic fire, its precision is good but not exceptional. It has an effective range of up to 800 metres. This model has had ghillie camouflage attached, making identification of the user more difficult. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PSO-1 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svdk">
		<text>SVDK .338</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svdk_descr">
		<text>The SVDK is a Russian precision rifle from the SVD rifle family originally chambered for the 9.3x64mm 7N33 cartridge. It was created to deal with targets which are too hard for standard 7.62x54mmR sniper rifles like SV-98 or SVD, such as assault troops in heavy body armor or enemy snipers behind cover. This is an experimental model, chambered in .338 Lapua Magnum in order to improve its efficiency against long range targets. It borrows some aspects from the SVCh-8.6, another SVD derived modern sniper rifle, also firing .338 Lapua Magnum. This model has been equipped with an old 1PN58 optic, though its night vision capability has been disabled without further upgrades. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1PN58 scope (integrated) \n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP suppressor \n\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rgm40">
		<text>RGM-40 Kastet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rgm40_descr">
		<text>The RGM-40 Kastet (English: Brass knuckles) grenade launcher is a stand-alone version of the Russian GP-30 grenade launcher with a telescoping stock, AK-type pistol-grip and flip-up tangent sights. It is a single-shot muzzle loaded weapon with a self-cocking trigger mechanism and offers a high degree of commonality with the GP-30. It was developed mainly for police use with non-lethal grenades, but it is also popular among soldiers. Standalone grenade launchers are regaining popularity, as mounted underbarrel increase a weapon's weight and change balance too much, decreasing practical accuracy and making it uncomfortable to carry them for prolonged time.\n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vp70">
		<text>HK VP70M (modified)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vp70_descr">
		<text>The Volkspistole ("People's Pistol") 70 is a semi-automatic pistol chambered in 9x19mm, developed by Heckler and Koch. It was designed as a cheap semi-automatic pistol that could be quickly repurposed into a burst fire machine pistol/PDW with the addition of a polymer stock. The VP70 was a fairly revolutionary design with many modern features. It was the first mass-produced polymer pistol, predating the Glock 17 by 12 years and uses a spring-loaded striker, also featuring a high capacity 18 round double stack magazine. The VP70M is the military variant with provisions to attach a stock, within which a three round burst mechanism and selector switch is housed. When in burst mode, the cyclic rate of the pistol is a blistering 2200 rpm, though even with a stock it is difficult to control and of limited usefulness. Normally without the stock the gun is semi-auto only, however this example has been modified to allow burst fire as a standalone, though this has removed its single shot capability. \n \n 
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_2022">
		<text>FN High Power</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_2022_descr">
		<text>The FN High Power is a 9x19mm pistol from FN Herstal, released in 2022 and representing the first "Browning Hi-Power" produced by FN since Hi-Power production ceased in 2018. The High Power is not a simple Hi-Power clone, featuring multiple improvements such as an increased 17 round capacity, ambidextrous controls, as well as changes preventing hammer bite. These changes, among others have resulted in a lack of parts commonality and magazine incompatibility with older Hi-Powers. Internally the gun differs from the original Hi-Power, though care has been taken to mimic the external appearance. While the original owner of this pistol had modifications made to allow for the mounting of an optic, the high cost of this weapon and that process led to the installation of a cheap and rather difficult to use reflex sight. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] reflex sight (integrated) \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor (after modification)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_sniper">
		<text>Sniper LR-300ML</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_sniper_descr">
		<text>While the regular LR-300 is best suited to close range engagements, this particular gun has been modified for longer range fire, increasing accuracy but decreasing rate of fire. This gun has also been attached with an integral suppressor, grenade launcher and telescopic optic. It can be assumed that this gun was going to be used as a cheap analog to the sniper rifle. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Trijicon TARS Scope (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svu_sniper">
		<text>OTs-03A SVU-A (military) </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_sniper_descr">
		<text>The SVU-A is a variant of the SVU rifle capable of automatic fire, designed on a request from the Russian Interior Ministry. Although the weapon is generally not suited for close-combat situations, the automatic fire has proven itself to be a reliable emergency solution for exposed marksmen. This particular model of SVU-A is favoured by military Stalkers, featuring a 1P59 3-10x Giperon scope and detachable suppressor. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1P59 Giperon scope (integrated) \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] KZRZP suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_slug">
		<text>Threaded SPAS-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_spas12_slug_descr">
		<text>The SPAS-12 is a dual-mode shotgun, designed for combat and anti-riot measures. It is employed by many special military and police units around the world. With its distinctive heat shield and folding stock, the SPAS-12 is an iconic firearm. Notable for its reliability and tactical flexibility. Despite its heavy weight, complex mechanism and considerable cost, it is in demand in the Zone due to its effectiveness against mutants. This model has a rifled bore which greatly increases its accuracy when firing slugs. However, using shot is not possible. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG scope (integrated) \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_556">
		<text>FN SCAR-L</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_556_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-L (Light) is chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, C-more Railway Tactical, EOTech scopes\n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_ak47_cheeki">
		<text>AK-47 (extended)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak47_cheeki_descr">
		<text>The AK-47 can be described as a hybrid of previous rifle technology. Mikhail Kalashnikov designed this automatic rifle combining the best features of the American M1 and the German StG44. The Kalashnikov is a gas operated 7.62x39 assault rifle and by far the most prolific small arm of the 2nd half of the 20th century. It had been and still is, in more or less modified form, manufactured in dozens of countries and has been used in hundreds of conflicts since its introduction. The 100 round magazine attached to this gun has a reputation for being impractical and unreliable, it is most often seen in the hands of those more concerned with showing off than practicality. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 1P29 scope \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 suppressor \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_saiga_m3">
		<text>Saiga-MK 5.45 v.30 (custom) </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga_m3_descr">
		<text>The Saiga semi-automatic rifles are a family of Russian semi-automatic rifles manufactured by Kalashnikov Concern (formerly Izhmash), which also manufactures the original AK-47 and its variants, Saiga-12 shotguns and Dragunov sniper rifle. Saiga rifles are a sport version of the Kalashnikov rifle, and are marketed for hunting and civilian use. This is a custom 5.45 example, fitted with a telescopic scope, 555mm barrel and automatic firing mechanism. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (after modification)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Mark 4 scope (integrated) \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ots27">
		<text>OTs-33 7.62x25mm </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ots27_descr">
		<text>This gun has been converted to fire 7.62x25mm, taking inspiration from the OTs-27 Berdysh (Russian for poleaxe), a multi-caliber semi-automatic pistol created as a candidate to replace the PM as a service pistol. the OTs-27-7 is the variant chambered in 7.62x25mm Tokarev, intended to take advantage of existing surplus, being one of the few modern high capacity pistols firing the cartridge. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] APS suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_trophy_ak">
		<text>Trophy AK</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_trophy_ak_descr">
		<text>A legendary weapon, it was previously owned by a legendary stalker who was said to be able to sneak anywhere, through any anomaly field and past any enemy. It is said that the previous owner used this weapon to kill mutants that were more dangerous than anyone else has ever seen. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] EKP-8-02 Kobra, 1P29, PSO-1 scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] TGP-A suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mk48">
		<text>MK 48</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk48_descr">
		<text>The Mk 48 (Mark 48), or Maximi is a lightweight belt-fed machine gun, firing 7.62x51mm NATO cartridges from a disintegrating belt of ammunition. It is manufactured by Fabrique Nationale Manufacturing, Inc., a division of FN Herstal based in the United States. The Mk 48 has been developed in conjunction with the U.S. Special Operations Command (USSOCOM), which has adopted the weapon and started its fielding process, beginning with special operations units. The design is based on an early 7.62x51mm NATO prototype of the FN Minimi - Maximi, modified to be a scaled-up version of the 5.56 mm Mk 46 Mod 0. Compared to older M60 and M240 based designs, the MK48 provides increased portability, though with slightly decreased performance. Receiver lifespan is only half that of the M240B, though reliability is still higher than the M60. This gun is also equipped with the Canadian C79 machine gun scope and a lighter paratrooper style stock.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ELCAN C79 3.4x scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

</string_table>