<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

    <string id="st_wpn_avt40">
		<text>AVT-40</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_avt40_descr">
		<text>The AVT-40 is a Soviet automatic rifle developed from the SVT-40. It was developed due to a shortage of machine guns, but the increased strain of automatic fire often caused breakages. Production was relatively brief, none were made after the summer of 1943. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[d_purple]• %c[ui_gray_2] PU special scope\n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_dp28">
		<text>DP-28</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_dp28_descr">
		<text>DP-28 is a Soviet light machine gun designed by Vasily Degtyarev in 1920s, chambered in 7.62x54mmR cartridge. It was adopted by Red Army in 1927, eventually becoming one of the most famous weapons of the WWII, later replaced by RPD. DP was cheap and simple LMG. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_duplet">
		<text>Duplet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_duplet_descr">
		<text>The Duplet is an improvised double-barreled shotgun manufactured by technicians in workshops near and in The Zone. It was produced by first stalkers in The Zone, since the black market of firearms was almost non-existent back then. Currently the Duplets are increasingly less common as more weaponry is available for cheap from traders and arms smugglers. It is a simple, crude firearm made from reinforced scrap metal and wood, with two barrels placed horizontally. The accuracy is low due to crude finish of the inside of the barrel, but it's not an issue since the gun is made for point-blank ranges. Two barrels hold one shell each and can be fired both in the same time. Due to questionable construction, unless one is very careful with the trigger, the weapon has a tendency to shoot both barrels at once. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_garand">
		<text>M1 Garand Navy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_garand_descr">
		<text>M1 Garand is a World War II-era semi-automatic rifle that was the service rifle of the US military. It is one of the most famous rifles in the world, widely considered the best service rifle of entire WWII - General Patton called it "the greatest battle implement ever devised". M1 was developed in 1930s by John Garand, Canadian-American weapons designer, and was adopted by US Army in 1936, replacing Sprinfield M1903 bolt-action rifle. More than 5 million of M1 Garand rifles were produced, and they greatly increased the firepower of US infantry squads compared to typical squad of other countries, who used bolt-action rifles. Mechanically, M1 is a gas operated firearm, using a long-stroke gas piston system with rotating bolt. It is fed by unique en-bloc clip holding 8 rounds. The M1 rifle was chambered in .30-06 Springfield round (7.62x63mm), which was standard cartridge back then, but small amount of these rifles was converted to .308 Win after the war (so called Navy Garands). \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m1carbine">
		<text>M1 Carbine (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_descr">
		<text> M1 Carbine is a lightweight, semi-automatic carbine that was introduced to US military during World War II. It was meant to be a primary weapon of rear echelon troops and those soldiers who did not need or couldn't carry a long and heavy infantry rifle like M1 Garand. It was very well liked in the WWII and after and is widely regarded as a reliable and effective weapon that is very easy to control even for less experienced shooters. Over 6 millions of these weapons were produced, more than any other US WWII weapon. After the war the M1 was used up until Vietnam war by US and even longer by more than 50 other countries. M1 Carbine was sold in big numbers on civilian market in US, leading it to be a popular rifle for gunsmiths to customize and convert to different calibers. While this tendency has slowed due to shrinking rifle stocks and an increase in value of original configuration rifles, many customized rifles still exist. This particular rifle has been adapted to fire the more powerful .357 magnum round, and is fed using 9 round Desert Eagle magazines. This variant is somewhat more common in the Zone due to the rarity of the .30 carbine cartridge. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1">
		<text>M1A1 Carbine (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_descr">
		<text> M1A1 Carbine is a paratrooper variant of M1 Carbine, a lightweight, semi-automatic carbine that was introduced to US military during World War II. It was developed specially for paratroopers, as it was very light and folding stock made it easier to airdrop with it. Apart from folding stock, the weapon is exactly the same. M1 Carbine was meant to be a primary weapon of rear echelon troops and those soldiers who did not need or couldn't carry a long and heavy infantry rifle like M1 Garand. It was very well liked in the WWII and after and is widely regarded as a reliable and effective weapon that is very easy to control even for less experienced shooters. Over 6 millions of these weapons were produced, more than any other US WWII weapon. Unlike the M1 Carbine, the M1A1 is a rare weapon and it is rarely seen outside museums and private collections, however, many fakes and reproductions exist. Among the more numerous conversions of the M1 Carbine is the 5.7x33mm Johnson cartridge. Parts from rifles of this configuration have been further used to adapt guns to the FN 5.7x28mm cartridge more commonly seen in the Zone, serving as a low cost alternative to the P90. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_grease">
		<text>M3 Grease Gun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_grease_descr">
		<text>M3 Grease Gun is a submachine gun chambered in .45ACP developed for US military during World War II. It was designed as a cheap weapon fit for rapid mass production in style of Sten and PPS-43 submachine guns. Before the M3, the US military's service submachine gun was Thompson M1928A1. It was a very good weapon, but it was very heavy and expensive in production. The M3 was made to fix this issue. Because of its crude, industrial aesthetics, the M3 was called the "Greaser" or "Grease Gun". Nonetheless, it was a relatively reliable weapon that was "just-good-enough" for war time. Slow rate of fire improved the controllability of the weapon and allowed for more accurate fire even in long bursts. The Grease Gun remained in service with US military up to Vietnam war, and was even used as late as in 1990s by Abrams crews because of their compact size. The M3 received an upgrade in the form of the M3A1, which simplified the gun, removing the charging lever among other changes. This one retains older, M3 pattern features. \n \n </text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m14dmr">
		<text>M14 DMR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m14dmr_descr">
		<text>The US Marine Corps Designated Marksman Rifle (DMR) is a semi-automatic sniper rifle adapted from the M14 rifle, similar to the M21 rifle of US Army. The differences from the M14 are an accurized match barrel, special synthetic stock with pistol grip, RIS rail for mounting optics and Harris bipod. The M14 is an American battle rifle chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO, which for a short time served as a service rifle of US military. Experiences of WWII showed a need for improvements over the M1 Garand rifle, with characteristics including higher capacity, modern ammunition and lighter weight. The M14 was meant to replace several weapon types, however, this proved to be an impossible task. The M14 was deemed "completely inferior" to the M1 Garand in a 1962 report by the Department of Defense comptroller, eventually being replaced by the M16. M14s with scopes are popular among hunters and sport marksmen. Few military M14 DMR rifles reached The Zone, where they are liked for very good optical sights, providing much better precision than low-power scopes of SVD rifles. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold 3-9x36 scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_c96">
		<text>Mauser C96</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_c96_descr">
		<text>The Mauser C96 (Construktion 96) is a semi-automatic pistol that was originally produced by German arms manufacturer Mauser from 1896 to 1937. The distinctive characteristics of the C96 are the integral box magazine in front of the trigger, the long barrel, the wooden shoulder stock which gives it the stability of a short-barreled rifle and doubles as a holster or carrying case, and a grip shaped like the handle of a broom. The grip earned the gun the nickname "broomhandle" in the English-speaking world, because of its round wooden handle, and in China the C96 was nicknamed the "box cannon" because of its rectangular internal magazine and that it could be holstered in its wooden box-like detachable stock. This variant is chambered in 9x19mm parabellum.\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m712">
		<text>Mauser M712</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m712_descr">
		<text>The Mauser M712 "Schnellfeuer" (rapid fire) is a select fire variant of the Mauser C96 featuring a detachable magazine. Production started in 1932 and ended in 1936, which has led to its unofficial designation of "M1932" by collectors. An extremely successful design, around 98,000 guns were made overall and they had their own series of serial numbers. Small numbers were supplied to the German Wehrmacht during World War II, who designated it the M712. This variant is chambered in 9x19mm parabellum and includes the iconic wooden shoulder stock. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_type80">
		<text>Type 80 (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type80_descr">
		<text>The Type 80 is a machine pistol designed in the late 20th Century by the People's Republic of China. It was developed by Norinco in the 1970s, influenced by the design of the German M712 Schnellfeuer and is chambered for the Type 51 cartridge (Chinese copies of the Soviet 7.62x25mm Tokarev cartridge), but it is fed by a 20-round detachable box magazine instead of the 10-round nondetachable magazine in a standard C96. It was designed to replace some of the PLA's Type 54s, especially the Type 54s in service in the Chinese special forces, as a small, light weapon which was required to be good at both attacking and personal defending, similar to that of a PDW. This particular firearm has had its external appearance modified to resemble the M712. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_add_mauserc96_name">
		<text>Change of calibre to 7.62x51</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_add_mauserc96_descr">
		<text>A complex, integrated alteration of the weapon's mechanical and automated parts, which allows its calibre to be changed at the cost of reliability.</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_stick">
		<text>PPSh-41 (stick)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_stick_descr">
		<text>A major infantry weapon of the Soviet armed forces during World War II, the PPSh-41 was a durable, low-maintenance weapon made of cheap, easily-obtained components. They utilise 7.62x25mm cartridge. This gun is equipped with a 35 round stick magazine and fires at a healthy 1000 rpm. \n \n </text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_gp100">
		<text>Ruger Redhawk .45 ACP/.45 Colt</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gp100_descr">
		<text> The Ruger Redhawk is a DA/SA, large-frame revolver that was first introduced in 1979 by Sturm Ruger and Company. Made from high-grade steel, it is available in a stainless steel finish. The Redhawk is reinforced to handle extra stress of high-pressure loads, making it very popular for use by handloaders as it is able to handle the most powerful .45 Colt and .44 Magnum loads easily. This model was designed to fire both .45 Long Colt and .45 ACP, though the rarity of .45 Colt in the zone has led .45 ACP to become dominant, however, due to the cartridge's shorter length it somewhat reduces the gun's accuracy. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_w500">
		<text>Smith and Wesson SW500 (modified)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_w500_descr">
		<text> The Smith and Wesson Model 500 is a five-shot, double/single action large-bore revolver originally firing the .500SW Magnum cartridge - the most powerful handgun cartridge in existence. The advanced design of the firearm helps in counteracting the recoil felt by the shooter. This includes the sheer weight of the firearm, use of rubber grips, the forward balance, and the use of a compensator. Nonetheless, the gun produces immense recoil. Due to the rarity of .500SW Magnum in the zone, ambitious gunsmiths have created modified copies, taking inspiration from the Russian RSh-12 revolver and converting the weapon to fire the subsonic 12.7Ã—55mm STs-130 cartridge shared by the ASh-12.7. These modifications have reduced the weapon's durability and lowered its potency, but the gun retains overwhelming power. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_gp100_sniper">
		<text>Ruger Redhawk .357 (scoped)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gp100_sniper_descr">
		<text> The Ruger Redhawk is a DA/SA, large-frame revolver that was first introduced in 1979 by Sturm Ruger and Company. Made from high-grade steel, it is available in a stainless steel finish. The Redhawk is reinforced to handle extra stress of high-pressure loads, making it very popular for use by handloaders as it is able to handle the most powerful .45 Colt and .44 Magnum loads easily. This model is chambered in the common .357 magnum cartridge and features a low power integrated scope. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_mosin_short">
		<text>Mosin-Nagant (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mosin_short_descr">
		<text>A basic version of the Mosin-Nagant with slightly worn interiors. The M1891/30 was produced for standard issue to all Soviet infantry from 1930 to 1945. It was extremely successful in World War II as a sniper rifle when it was equipped with a 4x PE or a 3.5x PU scope. Due to an abundance of these rifles and a relative scarcity of pistols, sawn-off Mosin-Nagants were often used by those who needed a small, concealable weapon. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity. \n \n </text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_sks_short">
		<text>SKS (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sks_short_descr">
		<text>The SKS is one of the first weapons chambered for the 7.62x39mm round. Replaced in Soviet front-line service by the AK-47 in the early 1950s, it remained in second-line service for decades and is still used as a ceremonial arm today. This rifle has had its barrel shortened, allowing it to act as a pistol, the gas tube has also been adjusted to maintain semi-automatic operation. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity. \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_short">
		<text>SVT-40 (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_short_descr">
		<text>The SVT-40 is a surplus semi-automatic rifle chambered in the 7.62x54mmR round. It saw widespread use in the Red Army and Wehrmacht during WWII. This rifle has had its barrel shortened, allowing it to act as a pistol, the gas tube has also been adjusted to maintain semi-automatic operation. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity. \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_avt40_short">
		<text>AVT-40 (sawn-off)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_avt40_short_descr">
		<text>The AVT-40 is a Soviet automatic rifle developed from the SVT-40. It was developed due to a shortage of machine guns, but the increased strain of automatic fire often caused breakages. Production was relatively brief, none were made after the summer of 1943. This rifle has had its barrel shortened, allowing it to act as a pistol, the gas tube has also been adjusted to maintain automatic operation. The shortened barrel results in greatly decreased accuracy and muzzle velocity. \n \n </text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_shorty">
		<text>Serbu Super-Shorty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_shorty_descr">
		<text>The Serbu Super-Shorty is a compact, stockless, 12 gauge pump-action shotgun. This one is based on a Mossberg 500 receiver and features a spring-loaded, folding foregrip. The Super-shorty is a shotgun that is used exclusively for personal defense, as it doesn't have enough range and velocity to be used effectively for hunting. It can however deal very high damage in short range and bring down most attackers in one well placed shot. It is regarded as a very effective weapon against mutants who rely on ambushes and quick leaps to attack their victim. Most stalkers prefer cheaper double-barrel sawn-off shotguns for this task, but the Serbu Super-Shorty has better handling and slightly higher capacity. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m1928">
		<text>Thompson M1928</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1928_descr">
		<text> The M1928 is a primary variant of the Thompson, an American submachine gun, invented by John T. Thompson in 1918, that became infamous during the Prohibition era, being a signature weapon of various crime syndicates in the United States. Later on it became the service weapon of US military as the primary submachine gun in the World War II. M1928 has front grip and muzzle device mounted by default. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_tommy_m1a1">
		<text>Thompson M1A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tommy_m1a1_descr">
		<text> M1A1 is a simplified military variant of Thompson, an American submachine gun, invented by John T. Thompson in 1918, that became infamous during the Prohibition era, being a signature weapon of various crime syndicates in the United States. Later on it became the service weapon of US military as the primary submachine gun in the World War II. M1A1 differs from M1928 mainly by simplified front handguard instead of front grip and lack of muzzle device. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_borz">
		<text>Borz</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_borz_descr">
		<text>The Borz ("Wolf") initially referred to a clone of the Armenian K6-92, however it has become an umbrella term applied to all improvised submachine guns produced during the years of independence of the Chechen Republic of Ichkeria. Only a few hundred Borzes were crafted at the "Krasniy Molot" plant, because production at this plant was stopped by the First Chechen War and moved into underground workshops. They are typically crude and inexpensive, with simple blowback operation, resulting in high rates of fire and low accuracy. The gun has fairly low durability, and may be best suited as a semi-disposable weapon, used to ambush and acquire higher quality guns from those that are better equipped.  \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[d_purple]• %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_w70">
		<text>Winchester Model 70 7.92</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_w70_descr">
		<text>The Winchester 70 is a bolt action hunting rifle and one of the most common hunting rifles in the world. It has been held in high regard by shooters since it was introduced in 1936, earning the moniker "The Rifleman's Rifle". The action has some design similarities to Mauser designs and it is a development of the earlier Winchester Model 54. It is available in multiple calibers and variants. the rifle is usually fed by a non-detachable internal magazine, with capacity varying based on caliber. Most common chamberings allowing 5 rounds, though larger rounds can reduce this to 4 or 3. While original 7.92mm rifles are exceedingly rare, made only for testing purposes and by special order, some after market conversions do exist.  \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[d_purple]• %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold VX-II 3-9x variable magnification scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m1903">
		<text>Springfield M1903A1 Marine Sniper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1903_descr">
		<text>The Springfield M1903 is an American bolt-action rifle originally chambered in .30-06 Springfield, serving as the US military service rifle before it was replaced by the famed M1 Garand. It was adopted in 1903 and fought in both World Wars, seeing use among the USMC in WWII due to an insufficient supply of Garands. It also saw use as sniper rifle, equipped with 2.5x or 8x scopes until the early Vietnam war. Two sniper variants were made, the M1903A1 "Marine" with 7.8x Unertl scope and M1903A4 with 2.5x scope. The Marine variant is considered to be a much better rifle, not only due to its high-power optic, but also its high quality finish and superior accuracy. Today Springfield rifles are used as target or hunting rifles all around the world. In the Europe Springfields are very rare, nonetheless they are sometimes seen. This specimen was rechambered to .308 Winchester likely as .308 ammunition is cheaper and easier to obtain.   \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[d_purple]• %c[ui_gray_2] Unertl 7.8x magnification scope (integrated) \n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_tiss">
		<text>OTs-12 Tiss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tiss_descr">
		<text>OTs-12 Tiss ("Yew Tree") (Russian:??-12 ????) is a Russian fully automatic compact assault rifle. It is chambered for the subsonic 9×39mm round primarily made for police forces. The rifle was developed in the early 1990s in TsKIB SOO of Tula designers VN Telesh and Yu.V.Lebedev. It is basically an AKS-74U re-chambered for 9×39mm, it was designed as alternative to the AKS-74U. The TsKIB SOO of Tula made several hundred of OTs-12s, which were transferred to the Interior Ministry security forces. Despite the good evaluation, the Tula Arms Plant did not establish a mass-production. They instead opted for a bullpup configuration known as OTs-14 Groza which became its successor. In the Zone, these guns and similar copies are commonly equipped with experimental 25 round magazines, which were cancelled early in production, but reproduced in the years since.   \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sten">
		<text>Sten Mk II(S)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sten_descr">
		<text>The Sten Mk II(S) ("Special-Purpose") was an integrally suppressed version of the Mk II. It was designed in 1943 and incorporated a ported barrel, lowering the velocity of shots fired to below the speed of sound without special ammunition. The suppressor heated up rapidly when the weapon was fired, and a canvas cover was laced around the suppressor for protection for the firer's supporting hand. Automatic fire was discouraged, as it can quickly wear out internal components, many of these guns had their selector switches welded to a single shot configuration. Original models of these guns are rare compared to the standard Mk II and can fetch decent prices if in good condition. The simplicity of these guns, have however lead them to be manufactured or converted from non-suppressed Stens, at relatively low effort and cost for those without access to more modern suppressed firearms.   \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sten_mkv">
		<text>Sten Mk V</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sten_mkv_descr">
		<text>The Sten is a family of British submachine guns chambered in 9x19mm and used extensively by British and Commonwealth forces throughout World War II and shortly after. They had a simple design and very low production cost, making them effective insurgency weapons for resistance groups. There were six variants of Sten submachine gun. The Mk II, the most common and well-known variant, was also most widely made, with about 2 million made during the war. The Mk V was one of the final and most refined versions of the Sten, made for paratroopers and special forces. It had wooden stock, front grip and also a bayonet mount, an uncommon feature for a submachine gun. Over four million Stens in various versions and configurations were produced. Many were homemade by partisans, freedom fighters and criminals. The Sten served for many years, eventually being replaced in many Commonwealth Countries by the Sterling, which shares a similar side mounted magazine configuration.   \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sten_762">
		<text>Sten Mk II 7.62x25</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sten_762_descr">
		<text>The Sten Mark II is the most common variant of the Sten, with two million units produced. While originally chambered in 9x19mm, the simple construction of the Sten allows it to be rechambered to 7.62x25mm Tokarev through a simple barrel  replacement and minor feed modifications. The most significant source of the rechambered Mark II was China, where they were known as the M38, which were typically fed from PPS-43 magazines and further simplified to an automatic-only configuration. This example is likely a simple aftermarket conversion, fed by 32 round SA 24/26 magazines.   \n \n </text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_vepr134">
		<text>Molot Vepr 7.62 (scoped)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr134_descr">
		<text> The Vepr (Ukrainian: "Wild Boar") is a semi-auto civilian hunting rifle based on RPK light machine gun and produced by Molot factory from Russia. Veprs found their way to The Zone as Stalkers often took their hunting rifles there, instead of buying military weapons on black market. They are well liked and sometimes preferred over AKs due to their higher accuracy and range. This variant is chambered in 7.62x39mm.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Zeiss 3-9x32 scope (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vepr134_camo">
		<text>Molot Vepr 5.45 (scoped)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr134_camo_descr">
		<text> The Vepr (Ukrainian: "Wild Boar") is a semi-auto civilian hunting rifle based on RPK light machine gun and produced by Molot factory from Russia. Veprs found their way to The Zone as Stalkers often took their hunting rifles there, instead of buying military weapons on black market. They are well liked and sometimes preferred over AKs due to their higher accuracy and range. This variant is chambered in 5.45x39mm and features lower recoil and improved accuracy. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Zeiss 3-9x32 scope (integrated)\n \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_winchester1892">
		<text>Winchester Model 1894</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_winchester1892_descr">
		<text>The Winchester Model 1894 rifle (also known as the Winchester 94 or Model 94) is a lever-action repeating rifle that became one of the most famous and popular hunting rifles of all time. It was designed by John Browning in 1894 and originally chambered to fire two metallic black powder cartridges, the .32-40 Winchester and .38-55 Winchester. This variant is chambered in .357 Magnum. \n</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_zm92">
		<text>Zastava M92</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_zm92_descr">
		<text>The Zastava M92 is a carbine developed and manufactured by Serbian Zastava Arms. The M92 is a shortened version of the Zastava M70 assault rifle, which is a modified copy of the Soviet AKM assault rifle. Unlike most rifle rounds which would otherwise experience a loss of velocity out of a shorter barrel, the 7.62x39mm round loses very little velocity when compared to a full length barrel. This makes it an excellent round for short-barrel rifles. The short barrel of the M92 may not lose enough velocity to even make a considerable difference when compared to the M70. This example comes in its base state with lightened parts, making it more suitable for long expeditions. \n \n 
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-4 suppressor\n \n</text>
	</string>

</string_table>